(Sheldon:)...I would request
that you that add this.
(Penny:)What is it?
(Sheldon:)You're kidding, right?
It's a bust of Sir Isaac Newton.
(Penny:)Oh, sure, sure.
Yeah, very Christmassy.
Excuse me, it's much more Christmassy
than anything you've put on the tree.
LEONARD:
Here we go.
December 25th, 1642, Julian calendar,
Sir Isaac Newton is born.
(Sheldon:)Jesus, on the other hand,
was actually born in the summer.
(Sheldon:)His birthday was moved to coincide
with the traditional pagan holiday...
(Sheldon:)...that celebrated the winter solstice
with lit fires and slaughtered goats.
(Sheldon:)Which, frankly, sounds like more fun...
(Sheldon:)...than 12 hours of church
with my mother followed by a fruitcake.
(Leonard:)Merry Newtonmas, everyone.
(Sheldon:)I sense that's not sincere,
although I have no idea why.
No, it's fine. Sir Isaac can go
next to this candy cane.
(Sheldon:)No, Isaac goes at the top of the tree.
(Leonard:)-No, he doesn't.
-I understand.
(Sheldon:)You dispute Newton's claim
that he invented calculus...